<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

<node name="/" xmlns:tp="http://telepathy.freedesktop.org/wiki/DbusSpec#extensions-v0">
  <interface name="org.freedesktop.NetworkManager.NetNsInstance">
    <tp:docstring>
      The Settings interface allows clients to view and administrate a
      specific instance of network namespace controlled by NetworkManager.
    </tp:docstring>

    <method name="GetDevices">
      <tp:docstring>
        Get the list of realized network devices in the network namespace.
      </tp:docstring>
      <arg name="devices" type="ao" direction="out">
        <tp:docstring>
          List of object paths of network devices present in the network
          namespace. This list does not include device placeholders
          (see GetAllDevices()).
        </tp:docstring>
      </arg>
    </method>

    <method name="GetAllDevices">
      <tp:docstring>
        Get the list of all network devices in the network namespace.
      </tp:docstring>
      <annotation name="org.freedesktop.DBus.GLib.CSymbol" value="impl_netns_get_all_devices"/>
      <arg name="devices" type="ao" direction="out">
        <tp:docstring>
          List of object paths of network devices and device placeholders
          (eg, devices that do not yet exist but which can be automatically
          created by NetworkManager if one of their AvailableConnections
          was activated) in a given network namespace.
        </tp:docstring>
      </arg>
    </method>

    <property name="Name" type="s" access="read">
      <tp:docstring>
      Name of the network namespace, as created in directory /var/run/netns.
      </tp:docstring>
    </property>

    <property name="Devices" type="ao" access="read">
      <tp:docstring>
        The list of realized network devices in the network namespace. Realized
        devices are those which have backing resources (eg from the kernel or a
        management daemon like ModemManager, teamd, etc).
      </tp:docstring>
    </property>

    <property name="AllDevices" type="ao" access="read">
      <tp:docstring>
        The list of both realized and un-realized network devices in the network
        namespace. Un-realized devices are software devices which do not yet
        have backing resources, but for which backing resources can be created
        if the device is activated.
      </tp:docstring>
    </property>

  </interface>
</node>

